

ABOUT ME

I have coached for about 11 years in Stockholm, working around youth and senior teams, regional and national teams. I have also focused a lot on player development skills and make sure to watch a couple of clinics each month to keep learning. Other than basketball I work as a computer programmer currently employed at Dewire, Knightec.

EDUCATION KTH 2016 - 2019

Master of Science in Engineering and Education, Stockholm

STI 2019 - 2021

Mobile app developer, Stockholm

CONTACT

+46737728175

erik-nu@hotmail.com

Tideliusgatan 36, Stockholm

Sweden

https://www.linkedin.com/in/erik-ugarte-786267159/

(athiscoache

ERIK UGARTE

Basketball Coach 300+ official games coached

WORK EXPERIENCE

Central Basket (current employment)

2012-2023
2019-2023
2018-2023
2021-2023
2016-2021

Huddinge Basket

• Youth coach 2013-2014

Stockholm Basket

•	District team boys U16	2017-2019
•	Regional team boys U14	2018-2020
•	Regional team boys U15	2019-2020

Swedish basketball federation

Men's U15 national team 2021-2022Men's U16 national team 2022-2023

CAMPS

•	Next Level Basketball Camp	2020	-2022
•	San Antonio Spurs Basketball Car	mps	2019
•	The Basketball Embassy Assemb	ly	2019
•	Central Basket Summer Camp	2017	-2022

LANGUAGES

Swedish
English
Spanish
French